Guide to the Lee S. Shulman Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- PROJECTS, Series 5
  - BioTAP: candidate, principal, superintendent lists, letters (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - BioTAP: Project Overview (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - BioTAP: Portfolio entries (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - BioTAP: Review Panel Meeting #1: excerpts from minority scholars (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - BioTAP: Review Panel Meeting #1: miscellaneous handouts (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - BioTAP: "Road Map" (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - BioTAP: student consent form (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - BioTAP: May 11, 1989 candidate meeting (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - BioTAP: June 28, 1988 component meeting (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - BioTAP: July 25-29, 1988 development team meeting (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - BioTAP: September 23, 1988 orientation: correspondence - candidate (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - BioTAP: September 23, 1988 orientation: correspondence - principals (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - BioTAP: September 23, 1988 orientation: correspondence - superintendents (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - BioTAP: September 23, 1988 orientation: correspondence - others (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - BioTAP: September 23, 1988 orientation: correspondence - recruiting (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - BioTAP:: September 23, 1988 orientation: directory (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - BioTAP: September 23, 1988 orientation: letter of agreement (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - BioTAP: Field Test Consent Forms (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - BioTAP: Handbook original (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Californial Beginning Teacher Assessment & Support Project Seminar, January 14-16, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Californial Beginning Teacher Assessment & Support Project Seminar, June 25-27, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Californial Beginning Teacher Assessment & Support Project Seminar, March 19-20, 1987 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Californial Beginning Teacher Assessment & Support Project Seminar, commissioned papers (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Californial Beginning Teacher Assessment & Support Project: follow-up on the August 4-5 meeting of the Interstate Consortium on the New Teacher Assessment and Support (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - "Californial Beginning Teacher Assessment & Support Project: New Teachers for California," [ca. 1987] (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - California Center for the Development of Candidate Based New Teacher Assessment, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - California Center for the Development of Candidate Based New Teacher Assessment, 1986-1987 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - California Center Budget (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - California Center Budget, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Field Testing for Elementary Mathematics, with Tom Bird's corrections, cover - exercise 6 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Field Testing for Elementary Mathematics, with Tom Bird's corrections, exercise 7 - general information (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - "100 Statements": Chronology, Matrix, Early Material (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - "100 Statements": iterations (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - "100 Statements": May 1989, Novermber 1989 transcripts (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - "100 Statements": Board Dimensions (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Final Analysis for Scoring History Videotape Critique - Kerdeman (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Final Analysis for Scoring History Textbook Example - Kerdeman (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - "Developing a Comprehensive Teacher Assesment Program: New Pylons on the Well-Worn Path," Ann Reynolds, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Case studies: Smith and Price, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Case study: Jeff Hinckley, 1987 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - OSU (Oregon State University) work samples (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Doc File - Rating, May-August, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Data: Portfolio Questionnaires to candidates, May 11, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Data: Examiner Debriefing, July 1989 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Data: Candidate Debriefing, July 1989 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - BioTAP: Handbook original, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - BioTAP: Publicity Form (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Debriefing of the Portfolio Experience, 5/11/1989 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Human Subjects/Video Consent Forms [ca. April, 1989] (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Assessment Center (AC) staff: May-June, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Assessment Center [March, 1989?] (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Pilot Test: April, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Head Staff: March, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Housing: May, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Bio material: November, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Bio Interview Protocol, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Memorandums, Notes, Agendas: January-May, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Memorandums, Notes, Agendas: September-October, 1989 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Biology Overview, May 1988 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Biology Component: Teacher background information sheet, June 1988 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Teacher Collaborator/Candidate Teacher Offers/Acceptances: May - June, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Potential Teachers: May-August 1988 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Principals and Superintendents: August 1988 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Teacher Regrets: February - June, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Sample Letters: October 1986 - December 1988 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - BioTAP Expert Panel II: August 1988 - February 1989 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - BioTAP Overview, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Documents, March - June, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - First Quarter Summary, December 1987 - March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Professional Assessment for Teaching: Interim Report of the Teacher Assessment Project, April 1988 (draft) (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Materials regarding Overview Report, March - April 1988 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - BioTAP Thursday meetings, March 1988 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - BioTAP staff meeting minutes, February - August, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - BioTAP meetings, October - December, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - BioTAP minutes, November - December, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - BioTAP: memorandums, notes, agendas: June 1987 - August 1988 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - BioTAP: agendas, notes, minutes: January - October, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - BioTAP: agendas and meeting notes, June - July 1988 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - BioTAP: agendas and meeting notes, June - October 1988 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - BioTAP: agendas and meeting notes, June 28, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - BioTAP: Review panel lists (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - BioTAP: Review panel meeting, August 18-20, 1988: logistics (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - BioTAP: Review panel meeting #1 agenda (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - BioTAP: Review panel correspondence (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Stanford University: Copyright & Patent Agreement, July 1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Miscellaneous: meeting notes, agendas, handouts, etc. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - TAP: memos and miscellaneous, 1986-1989 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Second Mock Board: History exercise descriptions and rating guides, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Second Mock Board: History rating sheet (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Second Mock Board: logistics (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Second Mock Board: memo to board members (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Second Mock Board: Math exercise descriptions and ratings guides (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Second Mock Board: Math rating sheets (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Second Mock Board: Scoring team materials (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Second Mock Board: Staff memos (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Second Mock Board: Transcript (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Data Analysis: correspondence to/from Pittsburgh group (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Data Analysis: S. Nelson-Barber candidate/exercise note file (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Data Analysis: Memos, minutes, etc. 5/1/88 - (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Data Analysis: Memos, minutes, etc. 3/1/88 - 4/30/88 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Data Analysis: Memos, minutes, etc. 1/1/88 - 2/29/88 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Data Analysis: Memos, minutes, etc. 9/1/87 - 12/31/87 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Data Analysis: October 13, 1988 - scoring meeting with ETS people (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Mock Board #1: Another try at 6 scoring dimensions, 10/14/87 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Mock Board #1: Codes used in the reports on candidates (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Mock Board #1: Glossary of acronyms for topic sequencing (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Mock Board #1: Math candidate report pages -- G, J, M, R, T (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Mock Board #1: Math candidate report pages -- K, M, P, Q, T (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Mock Board #1: Participants, misc. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Mock Board #1: 10/27/87 memo to teachers (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Mock Board Round 2: Transcripts (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - BioTAP reunion: transcripts, questionnaires, agendas, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - LAP Teacher meeting, 3/6/90: notes (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Field Test 1989: Spectator info. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Field Test 1989: Facilities - Escondido School (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Field Test 1989: Facilities - other rooms (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Field Test 1989: supplies (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Field Test 1989: memos (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Field Test 1989: forms (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Field Test 1989: correspondence: examiner recruitment (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Field Test 1989: Acknowledgement letter, examiners (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Field Test 1989: Examiner/Observer housing/food (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Field Test 1989: Thank you letters - examiners (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Field Test 1989: Candidate housing/food (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Field Test 1989: candidate than you letters (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Field Test 1989: videotaping stuff (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Field Test 1989: master lists (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - Field Test 1989: acknowledgment letters -- candidates (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - LAP/BioTAP agendas, release forms, June 1989 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - MacArthur Park catering: June 1989 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - TAP I/TAPII Conference, June 1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Alaska Group: May 21-24, 1989 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Minority Field Test Candidates: literacy and biology participants (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Minority Field Test Candidates: correspondence/consent forms - literacy and biology (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Sharon Nelson-Barber: "Cindy O" (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Notes from Candidate's Handbooks (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - BioTAP Development Team: General File (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Advisor's Statements (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Extra background information; unit planning forms; others (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - BioTAP Teacher Collaborator: Gene Gallock (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - BioTAP Teacher Collaborator: Stan Ogren (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - BioTAP Teacher Collaborator: Susie Turner (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - BioTAP Teacher Collaborator: Deborah Vollick (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - BioTAP Teacher Collaborator: Douglas Wong (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate A (with consent forms) (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Candidate A: Unit Planning (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate A (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate A (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate B (with consent forms) (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Candidate B: Unit Planning (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Community exchange, candidate B (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate D (with consent forms) (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Candidate D: Unit Planning (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Candidate D: Unit Planning (Cell Function, Chapter 4) (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Candidate D: Unit Plan excerpts (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate D (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate D (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate E (with consent forms) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Candidate E: Unit Planning (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Candidate E: Unit Plan excerpts (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate E, part 1 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate E, part 2 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate E (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate F (with consent forms) (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Candidate F: Unit Planning (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate F (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate F (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate G (with consent forms) (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate H (with consent forms) (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Candidate H: Unit Planning (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Candidate H: Unit Plan excerpts (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate H (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Community exchange, candidate H (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate I (with consent forms) (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Candidate I: Unit Plan (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate J (with consent forms) (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Candidate J: Unit Planning (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate J (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate J (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate K (with consent forms) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Candidate K: Unit Planning (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Candidate K: Unit Plan excerpts (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate K (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Community exchange, candidate K (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate M (with consent forms) (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Candidate M: Unit Plan (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Candidate M: Unit Planning (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate M (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate M (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate N (with consent forms) (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate N (with consent forms), cont. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Candidate N: Unit Plan (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Candidate N: Unit Plan excerpts (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate N (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate N (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate O (with consent forms) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Candidate O: Unit Planning (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate O (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate O (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate P (with consent forms) (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Candidate P: Unit Planning (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate P (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate P (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate R (with consent forms) (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Candidate R: Unit Plan (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate R, part 1 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate R, part 2 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate R (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate T (with consent forms) (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Candidate T: Unit Planning (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate T (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Community exchange, candidate T (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate U (with consent forms) (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Candidate U: Unit Planning (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Candidate U: Unit Plan excerpts (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate U (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange, candidate U (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate V (with consent forms) (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Candidate V: Unit Plan Excerpts (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate V (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Community exchange, candidate V (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate W (with consent forms) (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Candidate W: Cell Unit (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate W (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Training Material: Student Evaluation (W) (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Community exchange, candidate W (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - BioTAP Background: Candidate X (with consent forms) (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Candidate X: Unit Plan (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Candidate X (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Community exchange, candidate X (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Evaluation of Student Knowledge: Professional exchange confirmation (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Background Information: Candidate 26 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Literacy Project: Candidate 26, student 3 - David (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Literacy Project: Candidate 26, student, Tameka (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Literacy Project: Candidate 26, student, Marshawn (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Literacy Project: Candidate 26, student, Kendra (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Literacy Project: Candidate 26, student, Adriana (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Literacy Project: Candidate 26, student, Yusuf, Reshall, Vernon (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - On-Site Completion Interview: A-O-S Entry #2, Candidate 26 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Integrated Language Instruction, Candidate 26, Entry 1 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Integrated Language Instruction, Candidate 26, Entry 2 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Creating a Literare Environment: Candidate 26, Entry 1 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - CLE Data: Candidate 26 - photographs of field trip (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - CLE Data: Candidate 26 - photographs of field trip (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - CLE Data: Candidate 26 - photographs of field trip (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - CLE Data: Candidate 26 - photographs of field trip (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - CLE Data: Candidate 26 - photographs of field trip (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - CLE Data: Candidate 26 - photographs of field trip (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Open Entry: Candidate 26 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Candidate 26: exercises, June 1989 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Candidate 26: exercises, June 1989 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Background information: Candidate 27 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Candidate 27: students 1-5 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - On-site completion interview: A-O-S Entry 2, Candidate 27 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Candidate 27: A-O-S, students 1-3 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Candidate 27: Integrated Language Instruction, entries 1 and 2 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 27, entry 1 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Open entry: candidate 27 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Background Information: Candidate 202 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 202, entry 3 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: candidate 202, entry 1 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: candidate 202, entry 2 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Candidate 202: Portfolio Review (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Candidate 202: Exercises (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Candidate 202: Exercises (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - ILI Candidate 202: Entry 1 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Background Information: Candidate 100 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 100 - Entry 1 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Erik (Candidat 100 student) (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Jeremy (Candidat 100 student) (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Kara (Candidat 100 student) (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Luke (Candidat 100 student) (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 100 - Entry 2 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - On-Site Completion Interview: Candidate 100 - Entry 2 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 100 - Entry 1 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 100 - Entry 2 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Creating a Literate Envirnonment: Candidate 100 - Entry 1 (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Open Entry: Candidate 100 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 100 - Entry 2 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Candidate 100: Exercises (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Candidate 100: Portfolio Review (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Background Information: Candidate 205 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Assessment of Students (AOS): Candidate 205 - Entry 1 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 205 - Entry 1 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 205 - Entry 2 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Open Entry: Candidate 205 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Candidate 205: Exercises (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Candidate 205: Portfolio Review (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Background Information: Candidate 400 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 400 - Entry 1 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 400 - Entry 2 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 400 - Entry 3 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 400 - Entry 2 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Open Entry: Candidate 400 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Candidate 400: Open entry (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Candidate 400: exercises (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Candidate 400: Portfolio review (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Background Information: Candidate 1 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 1 - Entry 2 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Candidate 1: Entry 2 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - CLE data: Candidate 1 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - CLE data: Candidate 1 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 1 - Entry 2 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 1 - Entry 1 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 1 - Entry 3 (Box 50, Folder 13)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 1 - student 1 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 1 - student 2 (Box 50, Folder 15)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 1 - student 3 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 1 - student 4 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 1 - student 5 (Box 50, Folder 18)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 1 - On-site completion interview (Box 50, Folder 19)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 1 - Entry 1 (Box 50, Folder 20)
  - Candidate 1: exercises (Box 50, Folder 21)
  - Background Information: Candidate 4 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 4 - Entry 1 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 4 - student 1 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 4 - student 2 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 4 - student 3 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 4 - student 4 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 4 - student 5 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 4 - On-site completion interview (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 4 - Entry 1 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Integrated Language Instruction: Candidate 4 - Entry 2 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 4 - Entry 1 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 4 - Entry 1 (photographs) (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Creating a Literate Environment: Candidate 4 - Entry 2 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Candidate 4: exercises (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Background Information: Candidate 8 (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 1 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 2 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 3 (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 4 (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 5 (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 6 (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 7 (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - student 8 (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Assessment of Students: Candidate 8 - reflective statement (Box 51, Folder 24)